July Lopez

20 years experience, Award winning designer,

Tampa, FL - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/July-Lopez/c032e03c59ec909d

I have well over 20 years of motion graphics animation experience. I started my career in New York at MTV before moving on to ABC News, I designed for shows such as ABC World News Tonight, 20/20, and ESPN Sports. I've won Emmy Awards for Good Morning America and was also awarded the Peabody Award for News coverage of the 911 attacks. I then joined NBC as the Lead artist for NBC's Nightly News and the Today show before finally finding my place as Art Director for The Daily Show with Jon Stewart. After 8 years of Emmy award-winning comedy and creative genius with The Daily show staff, I decided to move to Florida. Here in the sunshine state I have done broadcast graphics, website production, creative branding, motion graphics and interactive media for many clients including HSN, Company Man Studios, Achieva Credit Union, The Tampa Bay Rays and The Florida Orchestra just to name a few.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Creative Director

JV Media LLC - Tampa, FL - May 2016 to Present

Creative branding. design. motion graphics

Motion Graphics Designer

Company Man Studios - Tampa, FL - May 2015 to May 2016

Motion Graphics. Branding. 3D design. video production

Motion Graphics & Digital Production Artist

HSN - Saint Petersburg, FL - January 2013 to May 2015

Broadcast Motion graphics. Digital website production.

Art Director

The Daily Show With Jon Stewart - New York, NY - May 2006 to November 2013

Art Direction. Broadcast motion graphics. live show production

EDUCATION

A.A.S in Pre-Law

City University of New York. B.C.C - Bronx, NY 1991 to 1993

SKILLS

Cinema 4D (10+ years), Adobe After Effects (10+ years), Adobe Illustrator (10+ years), Adobe InDesign (10+ years), Adobe Photoshop (10+ years), Adobe creative suite (10+ years), Presentation Design (10+ years), Art Direction (10+ years), Staff Management (10+ years)

LINKS

http://jvmediallc.net

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

DESIGN SKILLS RECOGNITIONS

01 Computer 02 Knowledge George Foster Peabody Award.

ABC Network News Coverage 9/11.

1 2011 New York, New York

Adobe After Effects Typography.

Adobe Premiere Compositing.

Cinema 4D Web Design.

Adobe Photoshop Image editing. Emmy Awards.

The Daily Show with Jon Stewart.

Adobe Illustrator Web usability. 8

[...] New York, New York

Adobe Audition Interface Design.

Adobe InDesign Social Media Platforms.

Adobe Lightroom

Emmy Awards.

Maya Good Morning America. ABC Network News

2

3ds Max [...] New York, New York

Final Cut Pro

Edward R Murrow Award

ABC Network News.

1

2013. New York, New York